http://www.thehenrycountybank.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Online Banking Login
Site Search
Search thehenrycountybank.com:
Main Menu
Privacy Policy
MISSION STATEMENT
The Henry County Bank's Mission is to meet the financial and financially related desires of its customers. In order to provide an array of financial products and services it becomes necessary to collect, use, retain, and secure individual customer information. As financial professionals entrusted with sensitive financial information, we will respect the privacy of our customers and will be committed to treating customer information responsibly and will comply with laws and regulations designed to secure that privacy.
WHAT DOES THE HENRY COUNTY BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we may collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number
Income
Account balances
Credit history
Credit Scores
Assets
How?
All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons The Henry County Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does The Henry County Bank share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purpose- such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes- to offer our products and services to you
No
We don't share
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
Yes
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes- information about your transactions and experiences
No
We don't share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes- information about your creditworthiness
No
We don't share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
Yes
Yes
What We Do
How does The Henry County Bank protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.
How does The Henry County Bank collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account
Apply for a loan
Give us your income information
Provide employment information
Show your government-issued ID
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes-information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply jointly to everyone on your account.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
*The Henry County Bank has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
*Nonaffiliates we share with can include investment companies.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
*Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies.
Other Important Information
For Alaska, Illinois, Maryland and North Dakota Customers. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization.For California Customers. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization. We will also limit our sharing of personal information about you with our affiliates to comply with all California privacy laws that apply to us.
For Massachusetts, Mississippi and New Jersey Customers.We will not share personal information from deposit or share relationships with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint Marketing - without your authorization.For Vermont Customers. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing without your authorization, and we will not share personal information with affiliates about your creditworthiness without your authorization.
To limit our sharing
The Henry County BankP. O. Box 72Napoleon, OH 43545
Please Note: You may contact us at any time to limit our sharing.If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share as described in this notice.
Questions?
Learn More!
Learn More!
Learn More!
© 2016 The Henry County Bank. All Rights Reserved.
